

Noor Al-Huda Ali

Project manager and software developer specializing in front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages, including Dart, Flutter, Reactjs, Python, Laravel, C++, C, CSS, Bootstrap, HTML5, OOP, JS, CSS, and MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.



Baghdad, Iraq in 😱





Work Experience



Software Developer

Al-Handle International Group

March 2022 - Present

.Software development.

.Web Designer.

.Mobile application.

.Hosting.



Mobile application developer

Polymath | A.M.S Group South Korea

July 2021 - Present Taipei, Taiwan

.Mobile application developer (Dart and flutter).

.AWS Authentication.

.Firebase Authentication.

.Development Planning.



Project Manager and Software Developer

Freelancer with Rabih Moussa at MBC groups

February 2020 - April 2021 Taipei, Taiwan

.Getting a specific project from A to Z.

.Study all cases of projects.

.Development planning and services.

.Organize and lead the project's team, define their duties, and deliver them on time.

.Web design and development.

.Web hosting and maintenance.

.Logo design and corporate typography stationery.

.Posters and brochures.

.Controlling and managing Your Website for Clients.

.Responsible for the photography team.

.Proactively participated in meetings and helped create new practices.



Full stack developer And **Development Planning**

Nissan Factory for Fiber

January 2019 - January 2020 Taipei, Taiwan

.Making, corralling, and managing company websites.

.Developing and maintaining the websites.

.Developing the planning and creating of SDLC for it.



Software Developer And **Project Manager**

Ministry of labour and social affairs

.Strategic planning and SDLC for projects.

.Communicate with people and try to help them.

.Helped optimize management by identifying workflow issues and finding solutions.

.Pitched ideas on how to improve performance and efficiency.

October 2017 - August 2019 Taipei, Taiwan



Project Manager

University of Technology, Computer Science, Information Systems

February 2016 - January 2018 Taipei, Taiwan .Giving lectures on C++.

.Giving lectures on Management Information Systems and helping colleagues understand them.

.Helped management identify workflow issues and find solutions. .Pitched ideas on how to improve performance and efficiency.

Education



2016 - 2021

Certifications

- Basics of programming websites held in the Department of the Computer Science/University of Technology.
 https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yw3Ooeg50DyGDAD98yOgIDMA_kxXInkK/view?usp=sharing.
- Full Front-End developer from UOTIC.
 https://drive.google.com/file/d/14w3Z3Egsn_DE5ZdBv2FNT5IJI6BrFke0/view?
 usp=sharing.
- Design in Adobe Photoshop 2020 with Aswar Company.
 https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ztqnUX4k8aDRBmwzUpjho_AW5BTLg-Rx/view?
 usp=sharing HTML.
- Certification in Solo learns the application.
 https://drive.google.com/file/d/1qHlkkMrXuU0bvd83J8JN-IK7o8r_cWw1/view?usp=sharing
- C++ Certification in solo learn application.
- MSNAC (MORRELL Switching & Architecture Course) in ASWAR Company.
- CS50X Harvard.
- Dart and Flutter in Udamy.
- UI/UX in Udamy.
- · Python Rest API in computiq.



2016 - 2020

University of Technology, Computer Science, Information Systems.

Graduated top of my class. The last certificate at the university.

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QWbGo0GWGtfRc86llPIOPS6_6yJRbD3e/view?usp=sharing.

Skills

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Excellent computer proficiency (MS Office– Word Excel and Outlook)
- Create educational
 entertainment content
- Create customized websites and electronic forms
- Teamwork
- Leadership

Languages

- Arabic Native or Bilingual
- English Intermediate
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- Project Management
- Software Development
- GitHub and Git
- Strategic Planning
- Full front-end developer
- SDLC Skills
- Communication Skills
- UX/UI Design & designin ads and logo

Powered by CakeResume